(Yin Jisheng)
(Zheng Liyu)
"Thunderstorm"
(alarm clock)
My head hurts
Scared me to death
What are you doing?
do you have something to say
I started working
well done
Hey, wake up first before going out.
Can it be eaten?
I'm looking for a recipe this time. Follow the recipe
delicious
I'll just say it
You seem to know how to clean the house too
I'm great at everything
What else is great about you?
Hey debtor
Go over and get some paper and pen
write it down
before paying off the surgery.
All rights reserved to Li Yizhao
All owned by Xu Zhenghan
are you ready
Use your body to pay off debts
Use your body?
Cooking, cleaning, laundry
About household chores
Daily salary 100,000 won
Right
Didn’t you say you are still working part-time?
This should not take a month
You can pay it off, right?
(Daily salary of 100,000 won for cooking, cleaning and laundry)
Leave it alone, I'll take care of it
Excuse me
what is that
Not what you see
Are you lying now?
No
I followed the recipe
Pour into pot and cook for 10 minutes
and
I also added the meat separately.
You did something amazing
Zhenghan
What's wrong
Is there anything else you're hiding from me?
No
Otherwise
Don't you remember?
remember what
What's going on
It's okay. Go to work quickly.
Let's go
hello
did you see
Really handsome, right?
He's the type who inspires maternal love
I really want to capture him
He should have a girlfriend, right?
There must be some. They all look so handsome.
Not necessarily. Maybe everyone thinks the same as us.
But actually he doesn’t have a girlfriend
Then I'll ask him how he feels after lunch.
OK
How should I ask?
Knock knock knock
Is there anyone living in your heart now?
go away
Let's go to dinner later
Do you really not remember?
(Li Yizhao)
What on earth is he talking about?
-Eat something cool next time. -So full.
-I ate too much -Failed to lose weight
Xu Zhenghan, did you eat by yourself again today?
Section Chief Park, you can’t force others now.
Sorry, Minister
Xu Zhenghan
A boss like our minister
Can't be found anywhere else
I told you not to do this
How is your father doing?
what
I mean representative
Ah…
he is fine
I will keep it a secret for you
OK thank you
I'll buy you coffee today
- Oh, really? - That's great.
You come too
Originally, I was the one who wanted to invite you.
Then I'll give you a treat at noon tomorrow
ok
-Oh, he's handsome today too. -What do you want to drink?
-As long as it's iced, it's fine. -Please give me a cup of iced tea.
-Very good. -Can we order cake?
-Didn’t you just eat a lot?
-It's okay. Just order if you want to eat.
Li Yizhao
Zhenghan
The drinks are ready
-Thank you -Thank you
-The minister's meal is tea, right? -Yeah
-Thank you for the treat. -Thank you for the treat. -Eat more.
Oops, got it
- Oh my God - Where...
There is tissue here
Is this enough tissue paper?
biting
Very obedient
you are drunk
It's so noisy
How come you are so white?
It's a mole
wait a moment
How
don't you like it
No
i like
X's
-How? -Why did he leave? -Xu Zhenghan
Xu Zhenghan deserves to die. You got into trouble.
Drunk and crazy
Li Yizhao
sorry
I really didn't know where your company was
Just because…
That's the only place that notified me of admission
Forget it
Really
I really don't know
Eat
I've already cooked
I told you what will happen if you cook again
I'm dead
sit down
sorry
I remembered
Ah…
It seems I'm...too horny
But that doesn't mean I don't pick anything
Shouldn't we sleep together?
I asked you if we slept together
No
You fell asleep later
You won’t resist anyone who asks you to
because i like you
Not allowed
Have you forgotten our contract?
all your rights
All belong to me
I can do whatever I want
So you are not allowed to like me
i know
Don't look at me like that
I'm already like this. I get seasick easily.
So I will wake up soon
Because it's always been like this
So just pretend you didn’t hear it.
what do you want me to do
What do you want me to do so that you will wake up quickly?
Because it was a mistake I made when I was drunk
i will help you
Do you hate me that much?
I'm asking you
Do you hate me so much that I like you?
It's not a question of like it or hate it
Yeah
I hate you like this
Just tell me and I will help you
No matter what method is used
kiss me
Is this enough?
I ask you if this is enough
Damn it
Didn't you ask me to do it?
No, I didn't know you would actually do it.
and
I didn't brush my teeth either
Then go brush your teeth quickly
What is he doing?
Are you satisfied?
thank you
What to say
Just brush your teeth
why take a shower
what
No reason
Don't even think about it
I didn't say anything, okay?
Go to sleep
I'm leaving
Li Yizhao
What are you doing?
When did he go out?
Who do you like?
-Good morning -Good morning
So who do you like more among the two?
I'm very confused
They both have different charms
Then let me choose a photo
That's it, you didn't bump into me
-True or false -Why did you suddenly change your mind?
If Xiuxiao is a wild Doberman Pinscher
That photo looks like a white Maltese, right?
Makes you want to tame him
The two of them seem to have a close friendship.
Right
It seems that he is not an ordinary boss or work-study student.
Didn’t Izhao just come to the cafe to work not long ago?
Did they know each other before?
Yes, I saw them coming to work together in the morning.
I've been feasting my eyes since early today
It's incredible
Do you want to go with your colleagues?
Well, why don't you take the elevator?
You guys go upstairs first
I want to go to the beach
let's go to the beach
I still have to go to work
What class do you take? I can arrange it for you.
I will really help you get rid of it
Zhenghan
Three cups of fresh tomato juice
Two iced vanilla lattes
mocha coffee
A cup of hot and a cup of ice
Right
Also want mint tea
Put two or three ice cubes
good
do you need money
If you still need money, just tell me.
How much can such a shabby shop give you?
your credit card
For you to use
Don't just take advantage of other people's food
Can it be sent directly to the office?
OK
I'll send it there for you
thank you
Mr. Zhang Xiuxiao
This is the information you want
Okay, thank you for your hard work
You won’t contact me at all, right?
(Xu Zhenghan)
After work chef restaurant
(Zhenghan)
(Chef’s restaurant after work)
hello
Is this Mr. Li Yizhao?
-Yes -This way please
Take a seat
However
Why are there only two of us here?
I booked the whole room
Because I want to have dinner with you alone
Didn’t you tell me not to like you?
I never said what I wanted to do with you
Just looking for you to have a meal
What's the matter?
Eat
(Zhang Xiuxiao)
Take it
pick up here
-Hello... -Li Yizhao, where are you?
where are you what are you doing
I'm here to have dinner with Zhenghan...
are you crazy
Didn't you say you were clear with that guy?
Did he insist on taking you there?
Is he going to play with you as he pleases again?
Repair effect is not like this
I'll pick you up now
Where are you talking?
Hello Li Yizhao
I'll call you later
Hello, take a photo
Li Yizhao
What's wrong
I'm so sleepy
What...
So are we going home?
I'm too sleepy to walk
What should I do?
why come here
so hot
Hey, you'll catch a cold like this
So boring
help me untie
hey what are you doing
pain
Li Yizhao
I obviously told you
all your rights
All belong to me
Isn't it?
Zhenghan
You can do whatever you want
Why are you wrapped in a quilt?
No
Did I do it?
You said you want others to know that I am yours at a glance
I don't even know
So you asked me to use my body to pay off the debt
That's what it means
I don't want to go I don't want to go
Have you slept?
Take him out quickly
Anyway, this is not Li Yizhao’s home.